Guide to the Houston Area Fiber Artists Records
University of Houston Libraries
Houston Area Fiber Artists Records
1968-2014
1971-2002
02/2014-013
Houston Area Fiber Artists
20.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection contains materials related to organizational structure of the Houston Area Fiber Artists (HAFA), such as meeting minutes, financial records, secretarial records, membership lists, and more. There is also extensive photographic documentation of various art pieces created by HAFA members, as well as a number of VHS tapes and DVDs showcasing this material.
Historical Note:
The Houston Area Fiber Artists (HAFA) was federated in 1969 as an organization involved in the creation of original design in fiber media with the purpose of maintaining and advancing fiber as an art form. Mediums included knitting, sewing, embroidery, and more. Profits from fundraising activities were used for scholarships and support of educational programs. In December of 2014, the organization disbanded and is now a focus group of the Contemporary Handweavers of Houston.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Houston Area Fiber Artists
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Financial records; Membership lists; Newsletters; Scrapbooks; Slides (photographs); Videocassettes
Topical Term:
Art -- Exhibitions; Art -- Study and teaching; Art -- Texas -- Houston; Artists -- Texas -- Houston; Textile fabrics
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Physical Characteristics or Technical Requirements:
This collection includes digital archival materials, which can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee at velee@Central.UH.EDU for more information.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials related to organizational structure of the Houston Area Fiber Artists (HAFA), such as meeting minutes, financial records, secretarial records, membership lists, and more. There is also extensive photographic documentation of various art pieces created by HAFA members, as well as a number of VHS tapes and DVDs showcasing this material.
Detailed List of Contents
- Media Records
  Scope and Contents
  This Series contains media in a variety of formats, including slides, VHS tapes, and digital materials. Sub-series 2 contains VHS tapes. Due to the fragility of the media, please contact curator Vince lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) to inquire about viewing the tapes. Sub-series 3, 4, and 5 include digital archival materials. These arrived in the archives in the form of CDs, DVDs, flash drives, and 3.5" floppy disks. The contents have been transferred off these fragile media, but the media type is retained in the finding aid to reflect the original format and organization of the files. The digital files can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) for more information.
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Photo Slides, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photo Slides, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photo Slides, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Photo Slides, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Photo Slides, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Photo Slides, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Photo Slides, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - VHS Tapes
    Due to the fragile nature of the media, please contact curator Vince Lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) with questions about viewing these materials.
    - Fiber Artists Conference: Rachel K. Clark, February 1993 (Box 2, Item 1)
    - Nature in Fiber, 1998 (Box 2, Item 2)
    - Style Show, 1993 (Box 2, Item 3)
    - Style Show, 1997 (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Style Show, 1990 (Box 2, Item 5)
    - Style Show, 1995 (Box 2, Item 6)
    - Fiber Artists' Style Show, 1989 (Box 2, Item 7)
    - Fashion Show, 1990 (Box 2, Item 8)
    - Rich Griendling Demo Tape, undate (Box 13, Item 1)
    - Fiber Artists of Houston Meeting, Linda Lewis Weaving, undated (Box 13, Item 2)
    - HISD Cable TV, undated (Box 13, Item 3)
    - Linda Lewis, undated (Box 13, Item 4)
    - HISD—Perspectives Report, undated (Box 13, Item 5)
    - Textured Treasures Style Show, undated (Box 13, Item 6)
    - BurdaStyle Fashions of the 1990s (Box 13, Item 7)
    - Art Institute of Houston Gallery Show, 1990 (Box 13, Item 8)
    - Pleat, Repleat: The Smocking Machine Pleater, 1993 (Box 13, Item 9)
    - Fairfield Fashion Show, 1994 (Box 13, Item 10)
    - Ann Hartley, Creative Collage Techniques, 1995 (Box 13, Item 11)
    - Ann Hartley, Creative Collage Techniques (copy), 1995 (Box 13, Item 12)
    - Lucia’s Garden—Natural Dyeing, 1996 (Box 13, Item 13)
    - Fairfield Fashion Show, 1997 (Box 13, Item 14)
    - Millennium Magic, 2000 (Box 14, Item 1)
    - Health Partnerships Part II, 2001 (Box 14, Item 2)
    - Fiesta and more…, 2001 (Box 14, Item 3)
    - Jane Sauer Maker Profile, 2002 (Box 14, Item 4)
    - HAFA San Juanita Garza, 2002 (Box 14, Item 5)
    - Small Learning Communities, 2002 (Box 14, Item 6)
    - Safety, 2002 (Box 14, Item 7)
    - HAFA Professional Development, 2002 (Box 14, Item 8)
    - “Norman Kennedy” Waulking, 2003 (Box 14, Item 9)
    - HAFA Style Show and Luncheon, 2003 (Box 14, Item 10)
    - HAFA Style Show and Luncheon, 2003 (Box 14, Item 11)
    - HAFA Style Show and Luncheon, 2003 (Box 14, Item 12)
  - CDs and DVDs
    The digital files from these CDs and DVDs can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) for more information. When possible, CD titles in this finding aid have been taken directly from hand-written notes or labels on the discs received. In other cases, the titles may have been supplied based on the group of materials in which the discs arrived. The collection also contained 3 CDs that appeared to be blank, despite being labeled. These were labeled "HAFA Backup, May 10, 2008", "HAFA May 2013", and "HAFA Stuff 6/8/06".
    - HAFA 2008 Portfolio Jan., January 2008 (Compact disc 1)
    - HAFA Show and Sale 2010 (Compact disc 2)
    - Instructions - HAFA Sale and Show Info, undated (Compact disc 3)
    - HAFA Numbered Garments 2006 (Compact disc 4)
    - HAFA 2006 Runway - Originals (Compact disc 5)
    - Linda Thompson, 2006 HAFA Style Show Garments (Compact disc 6)
    - HAFA 2006 Runway Edited (Compact disc 7)
    - Welcome and Underwriter’s Pres. - NWWC Feb. 05, 2009, February 5, 2009 (Compact disc 8)
    - Celebrating Our Creative Spirit, Linda J. Thompson, undated (Compact disc 9)
    - Linda Thompson "Afterwards" Federation Show 2012 (Compact disc 10)
    - 18 Hands Gallery Presentation PowerPoint Feb. 26, 2009, February 26, 2009 (Compact disc 11)
    - HAFA Presentation PowerPoint 2009 (Compact disc 12)
    - HAFA Portfolio 2013 (Compact disc 13)
    - Garments Night Meeting 2006 (Compact disc 14)
    - Conference Brochure Apr. 21, 2009, HAFA, etc., April 22, 2009 (Compact disc 15)
    - HAFA Stuff from Anastasia, undated (Compact disc 16)
    - Photos of Leaves Oct.10, 2007, October 10, 2007 (Compact disc 17)
    - HAFA copy of membership, May 6, 2004; June '04 Practice as of May 20; Picture of cap (Compact disc 18)
    - HAFA Dec. 2010, December 2010 (Compact disc 19)
    - HAFA Aug. 2010, August 2010 (Compact disc 20)
    - HAFA Aug. 2010, August 2010 (Compact disc 21)
    - HAFA 2011 (Compact disc 22)
    - Publisher Nov. 2011, November 2011 (Compact disc 23)
    - HAFA Nov. 2011, November 2011 (Compact disc 24)
    - HAFA Aug.-Sept., 2011, August-September 2011 (Compact disc 25)
    - HAFA Sept. 2012 and Publisher, September 2012 (Compact disc 26)
    - HAFA July 2012 (Compact disc 27)
    - HAFA Aug.31, 2013, August 31, 2013 (Compact disc 28)
    - HAFA End of 2013 (Compact disc 29)
    - HAFA June 2014 (Compact disc 30)
    - HAFA Membership May 2004; Newsletter Nov. 2004, May, November, 2004 (Compact disc 31)
    - HAFA Oct. 2004, October 2004 (Compact disc 32)
    - Board Meeting, Mail List, Newsletter, Sept. 2004 (Compact disc 33)
    - HAFA Newsletter Aug. 2004, August 2004 (Compact disc 34)
    - HAFA June/July 2004 (Compact disc 35)
    - HAFA Newsletter May 2004 (Compact disc 36)
    - HAFA Membership, undated (Compact disc 37)
    - Jan. 2005 HAFA, January 2005 (Compact disc 38)
    - Feb. 2005 HAFA, February 2005 (Compact disc 39)
    - Mar. 2005 HAFA, March 2005 (Compact disc 40)
    - Apr. 2005 HAFA, April 2005 (Compact disc 41)
    - May 2005 HAFA (Compact disc 42)
    - June 2005 HAFA (Compact disc 43)
    - HAFA July 2005 (Compact disc 44)
    - Aug. 2005 HAFA, August 2005 (Compact disc 45)
    - Sept. 2005 HAFA, September 2005 (Compact disc 46)
    - Oct. 2005 HAFA, October 2005 (Compact disc 47)
    - Nov. 2005 HAFA, November 2005 (Compact disc 48)
    - Dec. 2006, December 2006 (Compact disc 49)
    - HAFA Nov. 2006, November 2006 (Compact disc 50)
    - HAFA Oct. 2006, October 2006 (Compact disc 51)
    - HAFA Aug. 2006, August 2006 (Compact disc 52)
    - HAFA July 2006 (Compact disc 53)
    - May 2006 (Compact disc 54)
    - HAFA March 2006 (Compact disc 55)
    - HAFA Folder Jan.26, 2006, January 26, 2006 (Compact disc 56)
    - Dec. Jan. 2006 HAFA (Compact disc 57)
    - HAFA Address List Dec. 20, 2006; HAFA Email List; HAFA Members Xcel; HAFA USPS List; Labels Aug. 2006; Federation Stuff, undated; 2006 (Compact disc 58)
    - 2007 HAFA Newsletters (Compact disc 59)
    - HAFA Common Threads Folder Oct. 12, 2007, October 12, 2007 (Compact disc 60)
    - July 2007 Common Threads, Aug./Sept. 2007, July-Sept. 2007 (Compact disc 61)
    - HAFA Newsletter May 2007 (Compact disc 62)
    - May HAFA Newsletter 2007, May 2007 (Compact disc 63)
    - HAFA Newsletter Apr. 2007, April 2007 (Compact disc 64)
    - Mar. 2007, March 2007 (Compact disc 65)
    - HAFA Newsletter Feb. 2007, February 2007 (Compact disc 66)
    - Jan. 2007, January 2007 (Compact disc 67)
    - HAFA Info 2005-2006; May-June Newsletter (Compact disc 68)
    - Electronic Versions of CK Reg., Contracts, etc., December 21, 2010 (Compact disc 69)
    - Linda's Gallery, Creative Couture Garments by Linda (Compact disc 70)
    - HAFA 2003-2004 (Compact disc 71)
    - HAFA Conference and Show, PowerPoint Presentation 2009 (Compact disc 72)
    - Fed Dir HAFA 2008 (Dvd 1)
    - Nov. 5, 2008 HAFA Folder, Poetry, Stories (Dvd 2)
    - Houston Area Fiber Artists Video Style Show 2004 (Dvd 3)
  - Flash Drives
    The digital files from these flash drives can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) for more information. Some flash drives arrived with labels or tags. In these cases, finding aid item titles reflect these labels. In other cases, titles may have been supplied based on the apparent content (file names) of the drives.
    - HAFA, undated (Item 1)
    - Texas Federation of Fiber Artists, Powerpoint Presentation, 2009 Show, Juror: Tim Hardin (Item 2)
    - HAFA P.P. 2013 (Item 3)
    - HAFA, undated (Item 4)
    - HAFA webpages and membership list, 2014 (Item 5)
  - Floppy Disks
    The digital files from these floppy disks can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@Central.UH.EDU) for more information. When possible, disk titles in this finding aid have been taken directly from hand-written notes or labels on the disks received. In other cases, the titles may have been supplied based on the group of materials in which the disks arrived.
    - Back-Up Qdata FAH, 1998-2000 (Disk 1)
    - FAH, 1998-1999 (Disk 2)
    - HAFA Files, Quicken 2002, 2002-2003 (Disk 3)
    - Fiber Artist Sale, undated (Disk 4)
    - HAFA - Sale Books Spring Style Show, undated (Disk 5)
    - HAFA - Fin Data, June 12, 2002 (Disk 6)
    - FAH Auditor's Copy of Financials, 1999-2000 (Disk 7)
    - HAFA Financial Data, undated (Disk 8)
    - HAFA Sale Report, undated (Disk 9)
- Financial Records and Organizational Minutes
  - Financial Records
    - Financial Records 72-85, 1972-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records 86-87, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records 91-92, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records 92-93, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records 93-94 Part One, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records 93-94 Part Two, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Financial Records 94-95 Part One, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Financial Records 94-95 Part Two, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Financial Records 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Financial Records 96-97 Part One, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records 96-97 Part Two, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Financial Records 97-98 Part One, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Financial Records 97-98 Part Two, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Financial Records 97-98 Part Three, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records 97-99 Part One, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Financial Records 97-99 Part Two, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Financial Records 99-00 Part One, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records 99-00 Part Two, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records 00-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part One, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Two, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Three, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Four, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Five, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Six, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Seven, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Financial Records 01-02 Part Eight, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Financial Records 02-03 Part One, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records 02-03 Part Two, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Financial Records 02-03 Part Three, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Financial Records 02-03 Part Four, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records 02-03 Part Five, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records 03-04 Part One, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records 03-04 Part Two, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records 03-04 Part Three, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records 03-04 Part Four, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records 04-05, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes and Secretarial Record Books
    - Secretarial Records, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Secretarial Records, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Secretarial Records, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Secretarial Records, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Secretarial Records, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Secretarial Records, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Secretarial Records, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Secretarial Records, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Secretarial Records, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Secretarial Records, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Secretarial Records, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Secretarial Records, Part One, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Secretarial Records, Part Two, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Secretarial Records, Part One, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Secretarial Records, Part Two, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Secretarial Records, Part One, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Secretarial Records, Part Two, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Secretarial Records, Part Three, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Secretarial Records, Part Four, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Secretarial Records, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes, Part One, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Minutes, Part Two, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General Minutes, Part One, 1975-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - General Minutes, Part Two, 1975-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Minutes, Part One, 2002-2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Meeting Minutes, Part Two, 2002-2007 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Membership Records
    - Records and Membership Lists, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Records and Membership Lists, Part One, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Records and Membership Lists, Part Two, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Records and Membership Lists, Part One, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Records and Membership Lists, Part Two, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Records and Membership Lists, Part Three, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Membership Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Records and Membership, 2008-2014 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Art Shows
  - The Art of Stitchery/Encounter with Fibers, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fibrations '89: The Music of Your Soul, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fantasy in Form '87, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Creative Outerwear, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - MFAH Mike Metyko Lecture, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Style Show '89, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Shows, 1974-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Hansen Galleries Show, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cas Holmes Workshop, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Potential Exhbition Information, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Rites Writes Rights: The Year of the American Craft, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Valerie Campbell Harding, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Focus on Fiber Show, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Multiplicities of Fiber, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gallery Show Records, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Show Invitations and Programs, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Library Records
  - Library Records, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Entry Forms, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Creative Stitchers of Texas Yearbooks, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fiber Designers Yearbooks, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Open Chain Newsletters, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Fiber Artists Yearbooks and Programs, 1978-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Fiber Artists Yearbooks and Programs, 1989-1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Common Threads Newsletters, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Common Threads Newsletters, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fiber Artists and Quilt Guild Newsletters, 1970-1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - History and General HAFA Brochures, 1989-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rental and Loan Agreements, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Legal Establishment Paperwork, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Press, Notes, and Correspondence, 1998-2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Creative Stitchers of Texas Newsletters, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Texas Fiber Artists Membership Lists, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Creative Couture by Linda, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Common Threads Newsletters, 2009-2011 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Guest Books, Part One, 1987-1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Guest Books, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Postcards and “About HAFA”, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Fixtures International, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Houston Professional Women, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Storage Unit Rental, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Correspondence, 2002-2012 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - HAFA Yearbook, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Networking and Industry Contacts
  - Invitation Database and Industry Contacts, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Networking, Part One, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Networking, Part Two, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Networking, Part Three, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Resource Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Resource List Part Two, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- President's Records
  - President's Records, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - President's Records, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - President's Records, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - President's Records, Part One, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - President's Records, Part Two, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - President's Records, Part One, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - President's Records, Part Two, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - President's Records, Part Three, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - President's Records, Part One, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - President's Records, Part Two, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - President's Records, Part One, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - President's Records, Part Two, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Officer Responsibilities, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - President’s Records, Part One, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - President’s Records, Part Two, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1979-1980 Scrapbook (Box 9, Item 1)
  - 1973-1976 Scrapbook (Box 9, Item 2)
  - 1976-1979 Scrapbook (Box 10, Item 1)
  - 1991-1993 Scrapbook (Box 10, Item 2)
  - 1967-1972 Scrapbook (Box 10, Item 3)
  - 1993-1994 Scrapbook (Box 11, Item 1)
  - 1988-1989 Scrapbook (Box 11, Item 2)
  - 1987-1988 Scrapbook (Box 11, Item 3)
  - Fashion Show Portfolio, undated (Box 11, Item 4)
  - 1994-1995 Historian's Records Scrapbook (Box 12, Item 1)
  - 1995-1998 Scrapbook (Box 12, Item 2)